var questionInfo=[{text:"<p>In an effort to improve marine environments, artificial reefs are frequently used.  These artificial reefs can be built by using manmade objects that were previously built to serve other purposes such as metal structures, <b><mark>decommissioned</mark></b> ships, and even <b><mark>outdated</mark></b> tanks. The primary goal of artificial reefs is to protect marine life by providing a shelter under the water which in turn will increase the <b><mark>proliferation</mark></b> of fish. Whether the shelters provide adequate living environments for the ailing marine life impacted by human wastes is closely observed and analyzed.</p><p> The state of Florida in the United States is home to many artificial reefs.  With the inception of the Florida Artificial Reef Program in 1982, more than 8,426 miles of coastal areas of Florida have been a part of the artificial reef development. Many of them have been implemented to boost commercial fisheries by providing an ideal habitat for valuable fishes such as groupers and snappers. Researchers currently lack information to <b><mark>draw</mark></b> a conclusion on the effects of these reefs because they are still analyzing the reef’s influence on northern red snappers in the Gulf of Mexico. The resulting population of the northern red snappers will prove to be a conclusive evidence on the efficacy of the reefs since they are relatively long-lived fish commonly found near natural and artificial reefs as they <b><mark>age</mark></b>.</p>",details:[{question:"The word <b><mark>proliferation</mark></b> in the 1st paragraph is closest in meaning to",answers:["(A) preference","(B) problem","(C) growth","(D) damage","(E) health "]},{question:"The word <b><mark>decommissioned</mark></b> in the 1st paragraph is closest in meaning to",answers:["(A) compressed","(B) ordered ","(C) active ","(D) deactivated","(E) added"]},{question:"The word <b><mark>outdated</mark></b> in the 1st paragraph is closest in meaning to",answers:["(A) massive","(B) old","(C) stylistic","(D) powerful","(E) broken"]},{question:"The word <b><mark>draw</b></mark> in the 2nd paragraph is closest in meaning to",answers:["(A) argue","(B) give up","(C) seduce","(D) reach","(E) get rid of"]},{question:"The word <b><mark>age</b></mark> in the 2nd paragraph is closest in meaning to",answers:["(A) mature","(B) become young","(C) generate","(D) establish","(E) change"]},],cAnswer:[3,4,2,4,1]},{text:"<p>The advent of the magazine can be traced back as early as the 1600’s and has been serving a <b><mark>crucial</mark></b> role in spreading information as well as new ideas ever since. At first, its very existence was considered somewhat out of place. They did not contain enough news to be considered a newspaper and they were not classified under the category of casual or fun reading. Hence, they occupied a grey area in between the two, tailoring to enthusiasts who showed interests in very specific areas. At some point in the 17th century, publishers realized that a regularly, recurring distribution was needed. This is why magazines were also referred to as periodicals.</p><p>The introduction of the Gutenberg printing press in around 1450 set the stage for an entirely new spectrum of media distribution. Now, magazines were able to be mass-produced and were readily available for the common person to read. Prior to the use of the printing press, magazines were, for the most part, available only to a select few who could afford them. Not only were they limited to a few people, but they were also made available when the select few wanted them to be available. With Gutenberg’s creation, however, newspapers and magazines began to <b><mark>flourish</mark></b> among the common people, spreading information about important events and issues.</p>"+"<p>When discussing the origin of magazines, historians turn to a German theologian and poet Johann Rist who was responsible for creating the \“Erbauliche Monaths-Unterredungen\”, or \“Edifying Monthly Discussions,\” which is widely considered the world\’s very first modern magazine. The Edifying Monthly Discussions were periodicals released from 1663 to 1668. It included a wide array of philosophical analysis that were designed mainly for an <b><mark>intellectual</mark></b> audience. Although it was written for a limited amount of people, Rist\’s periodical soon inspired others to write more literary journals throughout Europe.  In France, consumer magazines played an important part in spreading political ideologies. Despite governmental censorship of religious and political periodicals, they frequently criticized the abuse of the Church as well as the <b><mark>incompetence</mark></b> of the bureaucracy. In this way, they somewhat contributed to the start of the French Revolution. While French magazines focused on the religious and political aspects, British magazines targeted the middle and working classes.</p>"+"<p>In the early 18th century, British magazines gained momentum. Some of the most famous publications included Daniel Defoe’s The Review, Joseph Addison and Steele’s the Spectator, and Sir Richard Steele’s the Tatler, all of which focused on delivering domestic and international political issues and opinions on a regular basis. These early publications would later be joined by magazines <b><mark>covering</mark></b> amusement and entertainment for the general public, gaining popularity that continues till this day.  </p>",details:[{question:"The word <b><mark>crucial</mark></b> in the 1st paragraph is closest in meaning to",answers:["(A) typical","(B) important","(C) unnecessary","(D) harmful","(E) new"]},{question:"The word <b><mark>flourish</mark></b> in the 2nd paragraph is closest in meaning to",answers:["(A) overcome","(B) scare","(C) thrive","(D) decorate","(E) influence"]},{question:"The word <b><mark>intellectual</mark></b> in the 3rd paragraph is closest in meaning to",answers:["(A) sophisticated","(B) ignorant","(C) appealing","(D) simple","(E) average"]},{question:"The word <b><mark>incompetence</mark></b> in the 4th paragraph is closest in meaning to",answers:["(A) determination","(B) inability","(C) qualified","(D) responsibility","(E) intrusion"]},{question:"The word <b><mark>covering</mark></b> in the 5th paragraph is closest in meaning to",answers:["(A) protecting","(B) hiding","(C) referring","(D) concealing","(E) handling"]},],cAnswer:[2,3,1,2,5]},{text:"<p>La Nina is the global weather condition that occurs every several years that results in below average water temperatures in the eastern Pacific Ocean. It often brings a <b><mark>cascade</mark></b> of events that shift weather patterns across the globe including changes in the location of thunderstorms and intensity of air pressures. In a La Nina event, below average water temperatures are driven westward from the coasts of South America, sending heavy rainfall to parts of Australia, Southeast Asia, and the Indian subcontinent while causing unusually dry and warm weather in parts of North America. This weather anomaly has troubled farmers throughout these regions and created a need for massive investments into the forecasting of its effects.</P><P>Currently, meteorological technology has made it possible to predict the occurrence of a La Nina well in advance. With information gathered from weather stations located around the world, scientists are able to detect the fall in surface water temperatures and make a fairly accurate prediction of when La Nina could come into effect. Meteorologists are also able to make some predictions on whether there will be a severe drought or heavy rain compared to normal levels, allowing the agricultural communities around the world to better prepare themselves.</P><P>Farmers in the Republic of Vanuatu, a small island nation off the eastern coast of Australia, are hoping to benefit from these weather predictions. Even now, the farmers are <b><mark>gearing up</mark></b> for another La Nina that could bring massive amounts of rain to their land. Previously, La Nina had caused huge problems for these farmers causing flooding, water-logged soils, as well as <b><mark>pests</mark></b> and crop diseases that resulted in massive food shortages and panic throughout the entire nation. Now, farmers are more educated about the effects of La Nina and have been taught various ways to <b><mark>minimize</mark></b> their losses. One way is to build an effective backyard garden that is able to <b><mark>withstand</mark></b> the enormous rainfall and another way is to plant crops that could survive the heavy rain, both of which can be very helpful for the farmers.</P><P>Contrary to the farmers in Vanuatu, American farmers could expect a dry, warm weather. In some cases, there can be a severe drought that could heavily interfere with the agricultural communities of the southern United States. Thus, farmers can choose an effective planting schedule and alter the types of crops they will plant according to these predictions. Statistically, farmers who carefully followed the weather predictions have benefitted tremendously by reducing their losses during times of drought and increasing their production during times of heavier rainfall than usual. Thus, weather prediction can play a significant role in farming.</P>",details:[{question:"The word <b><mark>cascade</mark></b> in the 1st paragraph is closest in meaning to",answers:["(A) series","(B) waterfall","(C) collapse","(D) progress","(E) possibility"]},{question:"The word <b><mark>gearing up</mark></b> in the 2nd paragraph is closest in meaning to",answers:["(A) cheering","(B) hoping","(C) reducing","(D) preparing","(E) covering"]},{question:"The word <b><mark>pests</mark></b> in the 3rd paragraph is closest in meaning to",answers:["(A) trouble","(B) animal","(C) plant","(D) insect","(E) nuisance"]},{question:" The word <b><mark>minimize</mark></b> in the 4th paragraph is closest in meaning to",answers:["(A) expand","(B) build up","(C) diminish","(D) descend","(E) put out"]},{question:"The word <b><mark>withstand</mark></b> in the 5th paragraph is closest in meaning to",answers:["(A) loosen","(B) assist","(C) hold off","(D) support","(E) surrender "]}],cAnswer:[1,4,5,3,3]},{text:"TOEFL Vocabulary Questions.<br/> <B>Choose a word that has the same meaning as the highlighted word</B> ",details:[{question:"The man has a very <b><mark>sturdy</mark></b> physique.",answers:["(A) odd","(B) extraordinary","(C) attractive","(D) robust"],},{question:"There will be a wedding <b><mark>ceremony</mark></b> and ensuing event.   ",answers:["(A) splendid","(B) pledging","(C) guaranteeing","(D) subsequent"]},{question:"His bold writing style was <b><mark>subjected</mark></b> to critical feedback from the readers",answers:["(A) open","(B) resistant","(C) durable","(D) reluctant"]},{question:"His ill health <b><mark>poses</b></mark> serious problems for the future",answers:["(A) resolves","(B) aggravates","(C) speculates","(D) presents"]},{question:"My sister and I had a <b><mark>consensus</b></mark> of opinion.",answers:["(A) agreement","(B) contradiction","(C) discrepancy","(D) negotiation"]},{question:"Her <b><mark>veracious</b></mark> statement convinced me to believe her.",answers:["(A) deceitful","(B) honest","(C) lengthy","(D) stifling"]},{question:"We have seen a technological <b><mark>breakthrough</b></mark> in this country.",answers:["(A) retrogression","(B) development","(C) controversy","(D) cooperation"]},{question:"The price of commodities <b><mark>fluctuates</b></mark> wildly from high to low.",answers:["(A) ascends","(B) oscillates","(C) persists","(D) deviates"]},{question:"It remained very difficult to <b><mark>procure</b></mark> food, fuel and other daily necessities.",answers:["(A) obtain","(B) provide","(C) accommodate","(D) yield"]},{question:"Haig went on to  <b><mark>elucidate</b></mark> his personal principle of war.",answers:["(A) emphasize","(B) spur","(C) instruct","(D) clarify"]},],cAnswer:[4,4,1,4,1,2,2,2,1,4]}];var answerInfo=[];var questionCount=1;function renderQuestions(){jQuery.each(questionInfo,function(index,value){$('.content-wrapper').append($('<div/>',{class:'main-text',id:'main-text-'+index,html:value.text}));jQuery.each(value.details,function(qIndex,qValue){$('.content-wrapper').append($('<div/>',{class:'answer-title',id:'answer-title-'+index+qIndex,html:questionCount+'. '+qValue.question}));$('.content-wrapper').append($('<div/>',{class:'answers',id:'answers'+index+qIndex}));jQuery.each(qValue.answers,function(aIndex,aValue){$('#answers'+index+qIndex).append($('<input/>',{type:'radio',class:'selectedanswer',id:'answer'+index+qIndex+aIndex,name:'answer'+index+qIndex,value:aIndex+1,textnum:index,qIndex:qIndex,questionNum:questionCount-1}));$('#answers'+index+qIndex).append($('<label/>',{for:'answer'+index+qIndex,text:aValue}));$('#answers'+index+qIndex).append('<br>')});questionCount++})});$('.selectedanswer').click(function(){var selectedValue=$(this).val();var textnum=$(this).attr('textnum');var qIndex=$(this).attr('qIndex');var questionNum=$(this).attr('questionNum');var result=isCorrect(textnum,qIndex,selectedValue);answerInfo[questionNum]={'qNum':qIndex,'correctAnswer':result.correctAnswer,'yourChioceNum':selectedValue,'result':result.result}});$('.summit-button').click(function(){$('.body-wapper').load('contents/result.html',function(){renderResult();$('.return-button').click(function(){var url='http://patricktoefl.com';location.replace(url)})})})}function renderResult(){var numOfquestion=questionCount-1;var correctCount=0;var resultArray=answerInfo;jQuery.each(resultArray,function(index,value){if(value){if(value.result){correctCount++}}});for(var i=0;i<questionCount-1;i++){if(!resultArray[i]){$('.score-details-wrapper').append($('<div/>',{class:'score-details',id:'score-details'+i}));$('#score-details'+i).append($('<div/>',{class:'score-header',text:i+1}));$('#score-details'+i).append($('<div/>',{class:'score-header',text:'-'}));$('#score-details'+i).append($('<div/>',{class:'score-header',text:'Not answer'}));$('#score-details'+i).append($('<div/>',{class:'score-header-wrong',text:'Wrong'}))}else{$('.score-details-wrapper').append($('<div/>',{class:'score-details',id:'score-details'+i}));$('#score-details'+i).append($('<div/>',{class:'score-header',text:i+1}));$('#score-details'+i).append($('<div/>',{class:'score-header',text:resultArray[i].correctAnswer}));$('#score-details'+i).append($('<div/>',{class:'score-header',text:resultArray[i].yourChioceNum}));if(resultArray[i].result){$('#score-details'+i).append($('<div/>',{class:'score-header',text:'Correct'}))}else{$('#score-details'+i).append($('<div/>',{class:'score-header-wrong',text:'Wrong'}))}}}var level;if(correctCount>23){level='Completion'}else if(correctCount>20){level='Introduction'}else if(correctCount>5){level='Foundation'}else{level='Basic'}$('.text-level').html('<span>'+level+"</span>"+" 반 수강을 추천 드립니다.");$('.text-score').text("You Scored "+correctCount+" / "+(parseInt(questionCount)-1))}function isCorrect(textnum,qIndex,selectedValue){var cA=questionInfo[textnum].cAnswer[qIndex];var sA=parseInt(selectedValue);if(cA==sA){return{correctAnswer:cA,result:true}}else{return{correctAnswer:cA,result:false}}}